I've been waiting for you.
"I've been waiting for you"?
Waiting for what?
The hand you held me with was so warm.
I can never forget it.
You must have heard
of the suspension bridge effect.
Studies show that
if someone is scared or startled,
they might misinterpret their emotions.
I was just startled earlier
because the lights suddenly went out.
So it was a slip of the tongue. A slip...
Well...
What slip of the tongue?
What exactly did you say wrong?
[Hongseok]
[Park Seonghyun]
[Shin Yongseok] [Shin Junseop] [Ha Yosep]
[Play Me]
Haven't you been too busy lately?
We don't even have time to meet.
The musical is keeping me insanely busy.
What was the slip of the tongue
you mentioned?
Ah... That was...
How are things with that actor?
We get along pretty well.
Really?
That's good.
I heard you even had conditions
to cast him.
Conditions?
Aren't there screening conditions
when casting actors?
Like regarding meetings
and contract duration.
Ah...
We didn't have those this time.
I'm heading off.
Tomorrow...
I'll come to pick you up too.
No, it's fine. I...
I'll come pick you up.
Who else will take care of you besides me?
Thank you.
I've been waiting for you.
He said he has been waiting for me.
Why did he only say it now?
Should I ask him to go to the movies?
Will he be very busy?
Yihyun, want to go to the movies
with me after rehearsal today...
Say hello.
This is Eden,
who will be working with you from now on.
Hello, I'm Shin Kyungmin, playing Eden.
Please take care of me.
Ah, hello.
I'm Kang Jae-on, playing Luka.
Then today's rehearsal...
You two can just rehearse together.
I hadn't heard there was
a separate casting for Eden.
Did you get selected through an audition?
It wasn't an audition.
A friend of the director recommended me.
This is my first time acting in a musical.
Please take care of me.
"What exactly do you expect from me?"
Then Eden's emotions must be chaotic
at this moment.
Even though he doesn't remember Luka,
his heart is unconsciously drawn to him.
Senior?
Ah.
Yeah, indeed.
-As for the details, we should ask the director...
-Then...
"In that case,
you might as well just leave."
He probably doesn't mean that.
He actually cares about Luka.
That's right.
He's actually asking Luka not to leave.
Well...
I'm sorry.
Huh?
What for?
I actually thought you were a parachute,
and your acting would be mediocre.
But you act really well,
and you're really passionate about it too.
I misunderstood you.
No worries. But...
What's your relationship
with the director?
I just saw you calling him by his name.
We were... friends from high school.
So have you guys been good friends
since then?
Hmm... No.
We reunited working on this musical.
I see.
You two must be pretty close.
Since you're asking him out to movies
after the rehearsal.
Friends don't really go to movies.
Though they might go to an internet cafe.
Ah, well...
Yihyun and I...
Shall we just...
quickly finish the rehearsal?
Sure.
Hello, Mr. Yoo.
I heard they've been friends
since high school.
But I don't know why,
they drifted apart for a while. It seems
they got close again after working on the musical.
From what I see...
What?
They don't seem like ordinary friends.
The way they look at each other
is quite intriguing.
Find a way
to break them up for me.
Yes.
But,
is it necessary to go this far?
Yihyun has been hurt a lot.
He can't do anything without me.
All right.
Just do as you are told.
I really like this line.
Also, would it be better
if I give a hug here?
How about we run towards each other
at the same time and hug?
Sounds good.
One, two.
Wait, shouldn't this light be replaced?
Yeah.
The floor doesn't seem very sturdy either.
D-Director?
I'll go get a hammer and some nails.
Ah...
I'll go with him.
This doesn't look like
they're just ordinary friends.
What's going on with these two?
Senior,
when you say this line,
how about you stand up there and call me?
When I hear the line,
I'll just turn around
and look at you like this.
This way there will be a height difference
in our line of sight...
I think it will be great.
Shall we give it a try?
Okay.
But this chair seems a bit wobbly.
Then let's just do this line.
It's me, Eden.
That day in the storm...
Senior, are you okay?
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Hey, shouldn't you go to the hospital?
How about we run towards each other
at the same time and hug?
This light...
The floor doesn't seem very sturdy either.
Why am I like this?
I was worried you'd be injured.
Just put it here.
Will you take it off yourself,
or should I help you?
Let me give you a heads up.
I have nothing to do with Kyungmin.
Why bring this up all of a sudden?
Just in case you misunderstand.
Are you mad at me?
No.
He's probably not mad.